Guide to the Student Government Association Records RG 5.15
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
- Series 23: Ursula Gleissner-SGA President (1991-92), 41195
  - Finance Board Min., Nov 91-May 92, 1991-1992; 41198 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Club Budget Report, May 91-Nov 92, 1991-1992; 41197 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Coaching Skills Test booklet, 1992, 1991-1992; 41196 (Box 11, Folder 46)
- Series 24: Joe DaSilva-SGA President (1992-93), 41188
  - SGA Min., April 92-May 93, 1992-1993; 41194 (Box 11, Folder 47-48)
  - SGA Min. (notebook), March 92- Mar 93, 1992-1993; 41193 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Legislation, April 92-May 93, 1992-1993; 41192 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - 1992-94 Legislation, September 92-May 94, 1992-1994; 41191 (Box 12, Folder 1-2)
    General note
    Folder 2 contains documentation of the direct allocation for the student activity fee.
  - 1992-94 SGA Constitutions, 1992-1993; 41190 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - 1992-97 Student Activity Fund: Forms/Memos, 1992-1993; 41189 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Series 25: Andrew Mouradian-SGA President (1993-94), 41179
  - SGA Min., May 93-May 94, 1993-1994; 41187 (Box 12, Folder 5-7)
  - SGA Min. (notebook), May 93- May 94, 1993-1994; 41186 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Swearing-In to SGA, 1993-1994; 41185 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1993-1994; 41184 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Finance Committee, 1994, 1993-1994; 41183 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - SGA Constitution & By-Laws, 1993-1994; 41182 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Club Lists & Contacts, 1993-1994; 41181 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - 1993-97 Fee Increases, 1993-1994; 41180 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Series 27: Martin Moore-SGA President (1995-96), 41117
  - SGA Min., April 95-May 96, 1995-1996; 41150 (Box 12, Folder 49-50)
  - SGA Min. (notebook), Sept 95- May 96, 1995-1996; 41149 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - SGA Senators & Members, 1995-1996; 41148 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Swearing-In to SGA, 1995-1996; 41147 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - SGA Elections & Petitions, 1995, 1995-1996; 41146 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - SGA Elections, Fall 95, 1995-1996; 41145 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Legislation, March 95-May 96, 1995-1996; 41144 (Box 13, Folder 5-6)
  - SGA Expenditures, 1994-96, 1995-1996; 41143 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Budget Requests, 1995-1996; 41142 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1995-1996; 41141 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Club Budget Balances, Spring 96, 1995-1996; 41140 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Budget Committee Min., 1995-1996; 41139 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - CLIO Budget Matters, 1996, 1995-1996; 41138 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Budget & Tuition information, 1995-1996; 41137 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Student Lie Committee, Jan-June 95, 1995-1996; 41136 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Student Life Committee Min., March 95-Nov 96, 1995-1996; 41135 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - New student Center Planning, 1996, 1995-1996; 41134 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Parking Proposals, 1995, 1995-1996; 41133 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Parking & Public Safety, 1996, 1995-1996; 41132 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Public Safety Access Authorization Forms, Feb 96, 1995-1996; 41131 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Teacher Evaluation, 1995, 1995-1996; 41130 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - NACA, 1995, 1995-1996; 41129 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Western Report, Nov 95-April 96, 1995-1996; 41128 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Information Tech Committee, 1995-1996; 41127 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - CSU Systems Computer & Network Use, Fall 95, 1995-1996; 41126 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Crisis Response Team, 1995, 1995-1996; 41125 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Notes (Chinese Culture class w/Dr. Young), Fall 95, 1995-1996; 41124 (Box 13, Folder 26-27)
  - CSU Day in CT, March 96, 1995-1996; 41123 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Misc. information, 1994-96, 1995-1996; 41122 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - 1995-97 Feb 97, 1995-1996; 41121 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - 1995-97 Student Rights & Judicial Matters, 1995-1996; 41120 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - 1995-99 Letters of Resignation from SGA, 1995-1996; 41119 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - 1995-99 Board of Trustees Min., 1995-1996; 41118 (Box 13, Folder 33)
- Series 28: Charles Pomeroy-SGA President (1996-98), 41069
  - SGA Min., May 96-April 98, 1996-1998; 41116 (Box 13, Folder 34-37)
  - SGA Min. (notebook), Oct 97- Apr 98, 1996-1998; 41115 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - SGA Motions & Proposals, 1996-1998; 41114 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Legislation, May 96-April 98, 1996-1998; 41113 (Box 13, Folder 40-41)
  - SGA Members, 1996-1998; 41112 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - SGA Member schedules, Spring 98, 1996-1998; 41111 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Swearing-In to SGA, 1996-1998; 41110 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Swearing-In to SGA, 1996-1998; 41109 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Petitions for SGA, 1996-1998; 41108 (Box 13, Folder 47-48)
  - SGA Elections, Fall 96, 1996-1998; 41107 (Box 13, Folder 49-50)
  - SGA Elections, Spring 97, 1996-1998; 41106 (Box 13, Folder 51-53)
  - Budget Requests, 1996-1998; 41105 (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Budget Requests, 1996-1998; 41104 (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Club Budget Requests, 1996-1998; 41103 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Club Lists, Spring 98, 1996-1998; 41102 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Club & Organization Fact Sheets, 1996-1998; 41101 (Box 14, Folder 2-3)
  - SGA Constitution & By-Laws, 1996-1998; 41100 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - SGA Legal Clinic Proposal (draft), 1996-98, 1996-1998; 41099 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Palpable Injustice, 1997, 1996-1998; 41098 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Title IX Case: Q & A, 1998, 1996-1998; 41097 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Student Activities Fund: Financial Procedures, Sept 98, 1996-1998; 41096 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Student Handbook, 1996-1998; 41095 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Student Life Committee, 1997, 1996-1998; 41094 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Student Advisory Board, 1998, 1996-1998; 41093 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - WCSU Faculty, 1996-1998; 41092 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Search Committee: Dean of Student Affairs, 1997, 1996-1998; 41091 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Greek Council, 1998, 1996-1998; 41090 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Campus Pride Committee, Oct 96, 1996-1998; 41089 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Annual Reports to Student Affairs, 1996-1998; 41088 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Alumni Association Min., Aug-Nov 96, 1996-1998; 41087 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Strategic Planning, 1996-98, 1996-1998; 41086 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Planning Committee, 1997, 1996-1998; 41085 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - CUCAS Min., June-Dec 1996, 1996-1998; 41084 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Student Technology Fees, 1996-98, 1996-1998; 41083 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Information Technology Council, Apr 97, 1996-1998; 41082 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - NACA, 1997, 1996-1998; 41081 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - O'Neil Center, Jan-May 97, 1996-1998; 41080 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Food Service, June 96, 1996-1998; 41079 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Forms, 1997, 1996-1998; 41078 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - UPBC, 1996- 1998; 41077 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - CT Bill Concerning Grad Assistants, Aug97, 1996-1998; 41076 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Focused Planning Status Report, 1996-1998; 41075 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - CSU Legislative Proposals, 1998, 1996-1998; 41074 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - University Foundation of Western CT, Inc., 1996, 1996-1998; 41073 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - University ITC, 1996-1998; 41072 (Box 14, Folder 32-34)
  - SGA Misc. information, 1996-98, 1996-1998; 41071 (Box 14, Folder 36-39)
  - 1997-99 SGA Roll Call, Aug 97-Dec 99, 1996-1998; 41070 (Box 14, Folder 40)
- Series 29: John Kaltschnee-SGA President (1998-2000), 41047
  - SGA Min., May-Dec 98, 1998-2000; 41068 (Box 14, Folder 41-43)
  - SGA Motions, 1998, 1998-2000; 41067 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Legislation, April-May 98, 1998-2000; 41066 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Legislation, March-Oct 99, 1998-2000; 41065 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - SGA Members, 1998-99, 1998-2000; 41064 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - SGA Constitution & By-Laws, 1998-99, 1998-2000; 41063 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - List of Students, Fall 98, 1998-2000; 41062 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Club & Organization Fact Sheet & Lists, 1998-99, 1998-2000; 41061 (Box 14, Folder 50-51)
  - Clubs Carnival, Fall 98, 1998-2000; 41060 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Book Exchange Program, 1998, 1998-2000; 41059 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - SGA Standing Committees, 1998, 1998-2000; 41058 (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - WCSU Summer Planning, June 98, 1998-2000; 41057 (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - New Student Orientation, Fall 99, 1998-2000; 41056 (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - University Senate Min., Oct 99- Jan 00, 1998-2000; 41055 (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - Academic Planning: Self Assessment, 1998, 1998-2000; 41054 (Box 14, Folder 58-60)
  - WCSU Foundation, 1998-99, 1998-2000; 41053 (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - WCSU Common Data Set, 1998-99, 1998-2000; 41052 (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - CSU Schools Media Items, 1999, 1998-2000; 41051 (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - CSU Chancellor's Report, 1999, 1998-2000; 41050 (Box 14, Folder 64)
  - Blank Ballots, Spring 99, 1998-2000; 41049 (Box 14, Folder 65)
  - SGA Folder, 1998-99, 1998-2000; 41048 (Box 14, Folder 66)
- Series 30: Elisa Beckett-SGA President (2000-02), 41040
  - SGA Min., Feb 00-April 02, 2000-2002; 41046 (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
  - Board of Trustees Reports, 2001, 2000-2002; 41045 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees (Central CT), May-June 01, 2000-2002; 41044 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees (Eastern CT), May-June 01, 2000-2002; 41043 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees (Southern CT), May '01, 2000-2002; 41042 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees (Western CT), June-July 01, 2000-2002; 41041 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Series 31: Jamie Gravius - SGA President (2002-04), 50435
  - Minutes, 2002, 57762 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Financial and Miscellaneous, 2002-2003; 57763 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Minutes, Nov 2002-March 2003, 2002-2003; 57764 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Student Life Committee, 2002-2003; 57765 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Student Center Board, 2002-2003; 57766 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Information Technology Committee, 2002-2003; 57767 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Executive Board, 2003; 57768 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Minutes, April 2003-May 2004, 2003-2004; 57761 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Student Activity Fund Vouchers, 2003-2004; 50436 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Swear-ins, 2002-2004; 57769 (Box 28, Folder 36)
    General
    Includes resignation letters
  - Club Budgets (3 folders), 2003-2004; 57776 (Box 28, Folder 37, 38, 39)
- Series 32: Catherine Ferrigno - SGA President (2004-05), 57770
  - Constitution, By-laws, Resolutions, 2004-2005; 57772 (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Minutes, Executive Board Meeting 1, 2004-2005; 57777 (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 2004-2005; 57773 (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - Swear-Ins, Resignations, 2004-2005; 57774 (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - Club Budgets, 2004-2005; 57775 (Box 28, Folder 44)
- Series 33: George Bates - SGA President (2005-2006), 50439
  - CUCAS, 2005-2006; 50443 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Purchasing Requisitions, 2005-2006; 50445 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - V.P. of Finance, George Babykutty, 2005-2006; 57778 (Box 28, Folder 45)
    Description of contents
    Contains meeting agendas, meeting minutes, budgets
  - Club budgets, A-E, 2005-2006; 57779 (Box 28, Folder 46)
  - Club budgets, F-M, 2005-2006; 57780 (Box 28, Folder 47)
  - Club Budgets, N-Z, 2005-2006; 57781 (Box 28, Folder 48)
  - Rules Committee, 1998-1999; 57782 (Box 28, Folder 49)
- Series 34: Imran Qazi - SGA President (2006-07), 50450
  - Application for Recognition As a New Student Organization, 2006-2007; 50446 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - By-Laws of SGA, 2006-2007; 50447 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Finance Budgets, 2006-2007; 50448 (Box 27, Folder 6-11)
  - General Resolutions of the SGA, 2006-2007; 50449 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Series 35: Imran Qazi - SGA President (2007-08), 50451
  - Application for Recognition as a New Student Organization, 2007-2008; 50452 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Student Activity Vouchers, 2007-2008; 50453 (Box 27, Folder 14-17)
  - Purchasing Requisitions, 2007-2008; 50454 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- Series 36: Edmund Breitling, Jr. - SGA President (2008-09), 50455 (Box 26, Folder 19-22)
  - General, 51466
    - CUCAS, 2008-2009; 50456 (Box 27, Folder 19-22)
    - Club Constitutions, 2008-2009; 50457 (Box 27, Folder 23-32)
    - Job Descriptions for SGA Members, 2008-2009; 50458 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Purchasing Requisition, 2008-2009; 50459 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Senate Minutes, 2008, 2008-2009; 50460 (Box 27, Folder 33, 35-36)
    - Senate Agendas, 2008-2009; 50461 (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - SGA Constitution, 2008-2009; 50462 (Box 27, Folder 38-40)
    - Sodexho Food Requests, 2008-2009; 50463 (Box 27, Folder 41)
    - Student Activity Fund Vouchers, 2008-2009; 50464 (Box 27, Folder 42-46)
  - SGA Club Budgets, 51406
    2011 Accretion
    - 91.7 WXCI, 2008-2009; 51465 (Box 27, Folder 47)
    - Accounting Society, 2008-2009; 51464 (Box 27, Folder 48)
    - Airsoft Club, 2008-2009; 51463 (Box 27, Folder 49)
    - Bacchus, 2008-2009; 51462 (Box 27, Folder 50)
    - Bauhaus Art Club, 2008-2009; 51461 (Box 27, Folder 51)
    - Biology Club, 2008-2009; 51460 (Box 27, Folder 52)
    - Black Student Alliance, 2008-2009; 51459 (Box 27, Folder 53)
    - Campus Center Board, 2008-2009; 51458 (Box 27, Folder 54)
    - Center Stage, 2008-2009; 51457 (Box 27, Folder 55)
    - Chemistry Club, 2008-2009; 51456 (Box 27, Folder 56)
    - Chinese Students and Scholars Association, 2008-2009; 51455 (Box 27, Folder 57)
    - Choices, 2008-2009; 51454 (Box 27, Folder 58)
    - Christian Ministry, 2008-2009; 51453 (Box 27, Folder 59)
    - Clio: History Journal, 2008-2009; 51452 (Box 27, Folder 60)
    - College Democrats, 2008-2009; 51451 (Box 27, Folder 61)
    - College Republicans, 2008-2009; 51450 (Box 27, Folder 62)
    - Colonial Yearbook, 2008-2009; 51449 (Box 27, Folder 63)
    - Conatus (Black & White), 2008-2009; 51448 (Box 27, Folder 64)
    - Delta Gamma Phi, 2008-2009; 51447 (Box 27, Folder 65)
    - Echo, 2008-2009; 51446 (Box 27, Folder 66)
    - Education Club, 2008-2009; 51445 (Box 27, Folder 67)
    - English Society, 2008-2009; 51444 (Box 27, Folder 68)
    - Gay Straight Alliance, 2008-2009; 51443 (Box 27, Folder 69)
    - Graduate Student Union, 2008-2009; 51442 (Box 27, Folder 70)
    - Graduating Class Affairs Committee, 2008-2009; 51441 (Box 27, Folder 71)
    - Greek Council, 2008-2009; 51440 (Box 27, Folder 72)
    - Habitat For Humanity, 2008-2009; 51439 (Box 27, Folder 73)
    - Herpetology Club, 2008-2009; 51438 (Box 27, Folder 74)
    - History Society, 2008-2009; 51437 (Box 27, Folder 75)
    - HPX Club, 2008-2009; 51436 (Box 27, Folder 76)
    - Humanitarian Travel Club, 2008-2009; 51435 (Box 27, Folder 77)
    - IMPACT, 2008-2009; 51434 (Box 27, Folder 78)
    - Ives Concert Flutists, 2008-2009; 51433 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Jazz Club, 2008-2009; 51432 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Latin America Student Organization, 2008-2009; 51431 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Management Club, 2008-2009; 51430 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Math Society, 2008-2009; 51429 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Meterology Club, 2008-2009; 51428 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Muslim Student Association, 2008-2009; 51427 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Newman Club, 2008-2009; 51426 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - O.W.L's, 2008-2009; 51425 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Pinney Hall, 2008-2009; 51424 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Place Where He Provides, 2008-2009; 51423 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Prisma, 2008-2009; 51422 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Program Activities Council, 2008-2009; 51421 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Reality, 2008-2009; 51420 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Roots and Shoots, 2008-2009; 51419 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Rotaract, 2008-2009; 51418 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Running Club, 2008-2009; 51417 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - SAAC, 2008-2009; 51416 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Sigma Chi, 2008-2009; 51415 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Social Science Journal Club, 2008-2009; 51414 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Social Work Club, 2008-2009; 51413 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Student Athlete Advisory Committee, 2008-2009; 51412 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Student Center Board, 2008-2009; 51411 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Student Government, 2008-2009; 51410 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Student Government Publicity Committee, 2008-2009; 51409 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Student Nurse Association, 2008-2009; 51408 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Tau Kappa Epsilon, 2008-2009; 51407 (Box 28, Folder 27)
- Series Appendix: Legal Size Documents, 40986
  - Legislation (Theriot, SGA President) Sept 73-April74, 1973-1974; 41039 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Club Accounts (Theriot, SGA President), 1973-1974; 41038 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Legislation (Boskello, SGA President), April 74-April 75, 1974-1975; 41037 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Legislation (Pavis, SGA President), April 75-April 77, 1975-1977; 41036 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Legislation (Selnick, SGA President) April 77-April 78, 1977-1978; 41035 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - List of Students at WCSC (Selnick, SGA President) 1977-78, 1977-1978; 41034 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Legislation (Lubus, SGA President), May 78-April 80, 1978-1980; 41033 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - U.S. Student Association (Lubus, SGA President), 1978-1979; 41032 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Misc. Student Information Material (Lubus, SGA President), 1977-80, 1977-1980; 41031 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Legislation (Saviano, SGA President), May 80-April 81, 1980-1981; 41030 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Legislation (Block, SGA President), May 82-April 83, 1982-1983; 41029 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Newspaper clippings (Block, SGA President), 1982-83, 1982-1983; 41028 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Legislation (Adley, SGA President), May 83-April 84, 1983-1984; 41027 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Legislation (Retalis, SGA President), Sept 84-April 85, 1984-1985; 41026 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Legislation (Gill, SGA President), April 85-April 86, 1985-1986; 41025 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Legislation (Alhage, SGA President) April 86-May 87, 1986-1987; 41024 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Legislation (Brentari, SGA President), May 87-April 88, 1987-1988; 41023 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Legislation (Testa, SGA President), March 88-April 89, 1988-1989; 41022 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Legislation (Snearly, SGA President) April 89-April 90, 1989-1990; 41021 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Legislation (Trotta, SGA President), May 90-April 91, 1990-1991; 41020 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Legislation (Gleissner, SGA President), May 9-April 92, 1992; 41019 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Ledger Pages, Budget, 1980-1981; 41018 (Box 16, Folder *)
  - Ledger Pages, Budget, 1982-1983; 41017 (Box 17, Folder *)
  - Ledger Pages, Budget, 1983-1984; 41016 (Box 18, Folder *)
  - Ledger Pages, Budget, 1984-1985; 41015 (Box 19, Folder *)
  - Ledger Pages, Budget, 1985-1986; 41014 (Box 20, Folder *)
  - Ledger Pages, Budget, 1986-1987; 41013 (Box 21, Folder *)
  - Ledger Pages, Budget, 1987-1988; 41012 (Box 22, Folder *)
  - Ledger Books: -Budgets & Balances (CGA), undated; 41011 (Box 23, Item 1)
  - Ledger Books: Mar 52, 1952; 41010 (Box 23, Item 2)
  - Ledger Books: -CGA Min., March 52- Nov 54, 1952-1954; 41009 (Box 23, Item 3)
  - Ledger Books: -CGA/SGA Min., Nov 54-March 58, 1954-1958; 41008 (Box 23, Item 4)
  - Ledger Books: -SGA Min., April 58-Jan 61, 1958-1961; 41007 (Box 23, Item 5)
  - Ledger Books: -SGA Min., Feb 61- Mar 63, 1961-1963; 41006 (Box 23, Item 6)
  - Ledger Books: -SGA Min., April 63-May 65, 1963-1965; 41005 (Box 23, Item 7)
  - Ledger Books: -Club Budgets, Sept 52- Jun 54, 1952-1954; 41004 (Box 24, Item 1)
  - Ledger Books: -Club Budgets, Sept 58- Jun 61, 1958-1961; 41003 (Box 24, Item 2)
  - Ledger Books: -Club Budgets, Sept 61- May 67, 1961-1967; 41002 (Box 24, Item 3)
  - Ledger Books: -Club Budgets, Sept 67- Jun 77, 1967-1977; 41001 (Box 24, Item 4)
  - Ledger Books: -Club Budgets, Sept 71- Jan 76, 1971-1976; 41000 (Box 24, Item 5)
  - Ledger Books: -Club Budgets, 1972-1973; 40999 (Box 24, Item 6)
  - Ledger Books: -Club Budgets, 1976-1977; 40998 (Box 24, Item 7)
  - Ledger Books: -SGA Student Loan Record Book, March 71-May 73, 1971-1973; 40997 (Box 24, Item 8)
  - Ledger Books: -SGA Members Record, undated; 40996 (Box 24, Item 9)
  - Ledger Books: Book, 1975-1980; 40995 (Box 24, Item 10)
  - Ledger Books: -Phone Logs, July 75- Apr 76, 1975-1976; 40994 (Box 24, Item 11)
  - SGA Frisbee, ca 1995, 40993 (Box 24, Item 12)
  - Club Account Records (Pomeroy, SGA President), 1997-1998; 40992 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Budget Requests (Kaltschnee, SGA President), 1998-1999; 40991 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Ledger Books: -Club Budgets, 1992-1993; 40990 (Box 25, Item *)
  - Ledger Books: -Club Budgets, 1997-1998; 40989 (Box 25, Item *)
  - Ledger Books: -Club Budgets, 1998-1999; 40988 (Box 25, Item *)
  - Ledger Books: -Club Budgets, 1999-2000; 40987 (Box 25, Item *)
- Series Appendix: Photographs, 40837
  - #1-Arconti, Jim & Mark Block, 1982; 40985 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - #2-Arconti, Sandi, 1978; 40984 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - #3-Bacchiocchi, Susan (?) & David Pavis, 1977; 40983 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - #4-Barchfeld, Justin, 1975; 40982 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - #5-Barchfeld, Justin, 1976; 40981 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - #6-Barrows, Holly, 1979; 40980 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - #7-Benoit, Suzanne (?) & Daryle Dennis, 1979; 40979 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - #8-Bersi, Robert (WCSC President) & Dr Laurence Fisher, 1978; 40978 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - #9-Bigham, Keith (?), Frank Grgach, & Rose Previti (?), ca.1975; 40977 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - #10-Block, Mark, 1981; 40976 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - #11-Bonacci, Maryann (?) & Jan Jervs, 1979; 40975 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - #12-Bonazzo, Sally (?), 1974; 40974 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - #13-Bonyai, Michael (?), 1980; 40973 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - #14-Braun, Gertrude, ca. 1978; 40972 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - #15-Brooks, Stephen, Peter Faass, & Dennis Patrick Martin, 1974; 40971 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - #16-Cahill, Kevin King, 1979; 40970 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - #17-Calbert, Cheryl (?), 1979; 40969 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - #18-Calbert, Cheryl (?) & Paul Devine, 1979; 40968 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - #19-"Celebrating WCSC Men's Basketball Team Victory", 1979; 40967 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - #20-Clambake-Beach w/ plane flying overhead, 1975; 40966 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - #21-Clambake-Conversation between students, 1979; 40965 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - #22-Clambake-Student eating clams, 1979; 40964 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - #23-Clambake-Student laying on the ground, 1979; 40963 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - #24-Coburn, Mike (Rev.), Josef Friedman, & father Mark Grimes, 1977; 40962 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - #25-Connlly, Mary & Jan Jervs, 1979; 40961 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - #26-Cuchara, Tom (?) & Cindy Pascale, 1979; 40960 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - #27-Cuneo, Charlotte & Ralph Zona, 1974; 40959 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - #28-Danbury House-Echo series on pollution in Danbury, 1971; 40958 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - #29-Dance Team, 1979; 40957 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - #30-The Debate Club, 1974; 40956 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - #31-Delo, Gailmari, Paula Rafael, & Susan Salvini (?), 1980; 40955 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - #32-Ducey, Richard (?), David Pavis, & Nancy Ryan, 1973; 40954 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - #33-Dunn, Peter, 1979; 40953 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - #34-The Echo staff, 1974; 40952 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - #35-Faass, Peter, 1974; 40951 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - #36-Faculty Senate, 1980; 40950 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - #37-Fairfield Hall, 1979; 40949 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - #38-Fisher, Laurence (professor), ca.1978; 40948 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - #39-Fisher, Laurence & Dr. John Leopold, ca.1978; 40947 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - #40-Frenette, Sue, 1979; 40946 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - #41-"Fun w/ a hose", ca.1980; 40945 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - #42-Goldstein, Collen (?), 1979; 40944 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - #43-Goodin, Joyce Lynn (?), Sheena Graham, and Audrey Johnson, ca.1980; 40943 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - #44-Grady, Mike & Rosemary Lewis (?), 1979; 40942 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - #45-Graham, Sheena, 1979; 40941 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - #46-47-Grasso Hall ribbon cutting ceremony, 1983; 40940 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - #48-Gutaj, Dorothy, 1979; 40939 (Box 26, Folder 3)